* [Other](javascript:void(0))

**Privacy Policy**

Effective May 16, 2018

The Terms of Service (EULA) can be found at https://www.bananatic.com/terms-of-service/

In this Privacy Policy we explain how we collect your personal data and why we do so. Also you will find here information about the usage of your personal data and choices that you have about your personal data.

This Privacy Policy applies to all Sedoc LLC’s services including mobile applications and websites. Should any change in the Privacy Policy be applied you will be notified by posting a notice or by email prior to change becoming effective. Your continued use of the Services after the effective date will be subject to the new Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about data protection or if you have any requests for resolving issues with your personal data, we encourage you to primarily contact us through email  [\[email protected\]](https://www.bananatic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Name of the company collecting the personal data (the controller): Sedoc LLC,  14 NE First Ave, 2nd Floor, Miami, Florida, United States of America

Which data do you provide us and which is collected automatically:

* Player nickname and email which are used to login to the website
* Facebook, Steam, Tweeter, YouTube identificators.
* Other data you choose to give us (such as information in player support tickets)
* Your IP address and mobile device identifiers (such as your device ID, advertising ID, MAC address and IMEI)
* Data about your device, such as device name and operating system, browser type and language
* Data we collect with cookies and similar technologies
* Coarse location data (country or city-specific)

The data is being archived till the account has been removed or till services modification (i.e. when you externally decide to remove Bananatic from you Facebook account’s services permissions). Please note that after cancelling the contract (i.e. deleting the account on Bananatic.com website) all data will be processed further but only for archiving purposes.

On Bananatic.com website only specific personal data can be visible for other users. Your login or posted comments will be visible for other users. Please not that these information can be used by i.e. search engines, which means that also viewers who are not Bananatic users can have an insight into content created via your Bananatic account.

Processing your personal data is essential to fulfill all the contract’s resolutions. It allows us to deliver to you all Bananatic services which are essential to take advantage of whole functionality. You may easily register and manage your personal account. We focus on simplicity of usage and technical support in order to improve your user experience. All gathered information are needed to answer all requests or complaints which you can deliver to us with contact form.

Our services are intended to be used by anyone over the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal data about or direct or target interest-based advertising to anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to use our Services. We will delete all personal data about a child under age of 13 if we learnt that we have collected such(in order to delete the data / account on the website, please contact the website support directly via a ticket or by e-mail [\[email protected\]](https://www.bananatic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)). All users who are 13 up to age of 16 will have to have a parent or guardians approval to use our Services.

We collect your personal data to:

* Monitor user’s activity and secure terms and conditions laws in order to counteract any frauds or Services misuse.
* Improve our Services (quality of services, functionality)
* Marketing purposes
* Processing payment transactions
* Creating statistics for analytic purposes.

Gathered information grants you the access to the website. Registering an account is equivalent to approving Sedoc LLC contract terms.

In some cases your personal data is being processed by Sedoc LLC’s partners. These partners process your data only at and according to Sedoc LLC’s instructions in order to provide the Service, such as hosting, player support, advertising, analytics and fraud prevention. In order to combat fraud and illegal activity, we may exchange data with other companies and organizations and provide it to public authorities in response to lawful requests.

We may also disclose your data based on your consent, to comply with the law or to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our players or others.

If you request, we will provide you a copy of your personal data in an electronic format. You also have the right to correct your data, request to have your data deleted (in order to delete the data / account on the website, please contact the website support directly via a ticket or by e-mail [\[email protected\]](https://www.bananatic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)), object how we use or share your data, and restrict how we use or share your data. Should you have any questions contact us directly via [\[email protected\]](https://www.bananatic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We will respond to all requests within a reasonable timeframe.

Like most online services, we and our partners use cookies and similar technologies to provide and personalize the Services, analyse use, target advertisements and prevent fraud. Please keep in mind that we gather those information only to develop our Services. In order to use our Services cookies have to be activated. Taking back the consent to cookies policy is equivalent to deleting account request (in order to delete the data / account on the website, please contact the website support directly via a ticket or by e-mail [\[email protected\]](https://www.bananatic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)).

Please note that in order to use YouTube (i.e. in Bananpedia section, where you are allowed to access your YT account and upload videos) and Google services in general you shall familiarize with Terms of Service (located at  https://www.youtube.com/terms) and Google Privacy policy (available at https://policies.google.com/privacy). We are using YouTube API to allow you to use some of the Bananpedia functionality. Our intention is to analyze if the movie belongs to a specific User and what is the number of current views for the uploaded video.

In order to help ensure a secure and safe user experience, we are continuously developing and implementing administrative, technical and physical security measures to protect your data from unauthorized access or against loss, misuse or alteration.

Should you happen to have any additional questions we will be glad to help you. Please contact us via contact form or e-mail [\[email protected\]](https://www.bananatic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* [FAQ](javascript:void(0))
* [Terms & Conditions](javascript:void(0)) [Privacy Policy](javascript:void(0))
* [Contact](javascript:void(0))
* [](javascript:void(0))

[Trustpilot](javascript:void(0))

© Copyright 2015

[](javascript:void(0))

Leaving? Please stay!

Get a Free Game! 

Random STEAM key for you!  
Register, go to "Spend Bananas"  
Click STEAM treasure to pick up your game!
